<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFirstProject</string>
    <string name="antman">Antman</string>
    <string name="antman_des">Scott, a master thief, gains the ability to shrink in scale with the help of a futuristic suit. Now he must rise to the occasion of his superhero status and protect his secret from unsavoury elements.</string>
    <string name="batman">Batman</string>
    <string name="batman_des">Batman is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics. The character was created by artist Bob Kane and writer Bill Finger, and debuted in the 27th issue of the comic book Detective Comics on March 30, 1939</string>
    <string name="blackpanther">BlackPanther</string>
    <string name="blackpanther_des">After his fathers death, TChalla returns home to Wakanda to inherit his throne. However, a powerful enemy related to his family threatens to attack his nation.</string>
    <string name="bucky">Bucky</string>
    <string name="bucky_des">James Buchanan "Bucky" Barnes is a character appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Originally introduced as a sidekick to Captain America, the character was created by Joe Simon and Jack Kirby and first appeared in Captain America Comics #1</string>
    <string name="cap_america">Captain America</string>
    <string name="cap_america_des">Captain America is a superhero created by Joe Simon and Jack Kirby who appears in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character first appeared in Captain America Comics #1, published on December 20, 1940, by Timely Comics, a corporate predecessor to Marvel.</string>
    <string name="deadpool">Deadpool</string>
    <string name="deadpool_des">Deadpool is a 2016 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics character of the same name. Distributed by 20th Century Fox, it is a spin-off of the X-Men film series and its eighth installment overall.</string>
    <string name="doctorstrange">Doctor Strange</string>
    <string name="doctorstrange_des">In an accident, Stephen Strange, a famous neurosurgeon, loses the ability to use his hands. He goes to visit the mysterious Ancient One to heal himself and becomes a great sorcerer under her tutelage.</string>
    <string name="falcon">Falcon</string>
    <string name="falcon_des">The Falcon is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. The character was introduced by writer-editor Stan Lee and artist Gene Colan in Captain America #117, and was the first Black American superhero in mainstream comic books.</string>
    <string name="hawkeye">Hawkeye</string>
    <string name="hawkeye_des">Hawkeye is a character appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by writer Stan Lee and artist Don Heck, the character first appeared as a supervillain in Tales of Suspense #57 and later joined the Avengers as a superhero in The Avengers #16</string>
    <string name="hulk">Hulk</string>
    <string name="hulk_des">The Hulk is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by writer Stan Lee and artist Jack Kirby, the character first appeared in the debut issue of The Incredible Hulk</string>
    <string name="ironman">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="ironman_des">When Tony Stark, an industrialist, is captured, he constructs a high-tech armoured suit to escape. Once he manages to escape, he decides to use his suit to fight against evil forces to save the world.</string>
    <string name="loki">Loki</string>
    <string name="loki_des">After stealing the Tesseract, Loki comes into contact with a mysterious organization that gives him an ominous ultimatum, either fix the timeline or cease to exist completely.</string>
    <string name="moon">Moon Knight</string>
    <string name="moon_des">Steven Grant and mercenary Marc Spector investigate the mysteries of the Egyptian gods from inside the same body.</string>
    <string name="quill">Quill</string>
    <string name="quill_des">Christopher Michael Pratt is an American actor. Pratt rose to prominence in the late 2000s for playing Andy Dwyer in the NBC sitcom Parks and Recreation. He also appeared in The WB drama series Everwood and had supporting roles in the films Wanted, Jennifers Body, Moneyball, Zero Dark Thirty, and Her.</string>
    <string name="shangchi">Shang Chi</string>
    <string name="shangchi_des">Shang-Chi, a martial artist, lives a quiet life after he leaves his father and the shadowy Ten Rings organisation behind. Years later, he is forced to confront his past when the Ten Rings attack him.</string>
    <string name="spiderman">Spider Man</string>
    <string name="spiderman_des">Spider-Man is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by writer-editor Stan Lee and artist Steve Ditko, he first appeared in the anthology comic book Amazing Fantasy #15 in the Silver Age of Comic Books.</string>
    <string name="thanos">Thanos</string>
    <string name="thanos_des">Thanos is a supervillain appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by writer-artist Jim Starlin, the character first appeared in The Invincible Iron Man #55. An Eternal–Deviant warlord from the moon Titan, Thanos is regarded as one of the most powerful beings in the Marvel Universe.</string>
    <string name="thor">Thor</string>
    <string name="thor_des">Thor Odinson is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by artist Jack Kirby, writer Stan Lee, and scripter Larry Lieber, the character first appeared in Journey into Mystery #83 (1962) and first received his own title with Thor #126 (1966).</string>
    <string name="vision">Vision</string>
    <string name="vision_des">The Vision is a superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. Created by Roy Thomas and artist John Buscema, the character first appeared in The Avengers #57. The Vision is loosely based on the Timely Comics character of the same name who was an alien from another dimension.</string>
    <string name="wanda">Wanda</string>
    <string name="wanda_des">Wanda Maximoff is a character primarily portrayed by Elizabeth Olsen in the Marvel Cinematic Universe media franchise based on the Marvel Comics character of the same name. Wanda is initially depicted as a Sokovian refugee who, along with her twin brother Pietro, volunteers to be experimented on by Hydra.</string>
</resources>